in diet or individualism and western countries at least
在饮食或个人主义方面，至少在西方国家
there could be increasing churn and regards to social isolation
可能会增加流失率，并考虑到社会孤立
mission so happening with the elderly drop of oil and retirement words the
老人油下降和退休的话这样的任务发生了
price of interaction with children and grandchildren de raichu busy with live
与孩子和孙子雷赖丘忙于生活的互动的价格
with your session of social isolation happening among people from other age groups that
与其他年龄段的人之间发生的社会隔离感
situation an 11 in the morning in post and preferred over e-fiber
情况是上午11点发布，比电子纤维更可取
socialife social interactions half eat chance ose price and if you're not
社交活动社交活动有一半会吞噬机会价格，如果您不愿意
willing to pay the price how and whether this is a single cells from
愿意为此付出代价以及如何从
other people to be com lo nerds what you unfortunately after i felt and
在我感到和
loneliness so teams at the options how it ever got there
寂寞让团队可以选择如何到达那里
there is the misery of social isolation of the
存在社会隔离的痛苦
misery of being connected with people now let's talk about this
现在与人交往的痛苦
[Music] deskwriter body your research
[音乐]主持人将您的研究成果
that shows the detrimental effect of loneliness and or mental and physical
表现出孤独和/或精神和身体上的有害影响
half what despite the negative effect many people chose to rather not spend
尽管有负面影响，但很多人还是选择不花钱的一半
too much time with others when you click the comment section below my
单击我下面的评论部分时，与他人在一起的时间过多
video is about solitude it strikes with how many people even descried him as
视频是关于孤独的，它被多少人形容为
looners' and darcy dc perfectly happy this way
这样的傻瓜和达西DC完全开心
however he does the science of loneliness and the feeling of not being
但是他从事孤独的科学和不被人感觉的科学
so well the word template ines it is people aren't hard to fight
很好的单词模板ines它是人们不难战斗
know that there about seven trillion of them on this planet
知道在这个星球上大约有七万亿
so for some reason why choose to biologist and who don't let other people in your
因此出于某些原因，为什么选择生物学家，谁不让您的其他人
life easily kut this bbq aren't willing to
生活很容易让这个烧烤不愿
pay the price that comes with socializing
付出社交带来的代价
after spending a few months in a scarf and hat collectivist fabrics
在围巾和帽子收藏家的面料上呆了几个月后
culture is every important factor for individualistic society is that we don't
文化是个人主义社会的每个重要因素是我们不
need each other in a way that the collective
以集体的方式互相需要
to experience it first that the six percent chance
首先体验6％的机会
or is love big pro is that there have been people to hang out with the cause of
还是爱的最大支持者是，有人与
close family thai large and accessible social groups
亲密的家庭，泰国庞大而可及的社会群体
solidarity your man no birth of the many people you find on the street in one
团结你的男人不会在大街上找到很多人
guesthouse ice age for example oil peak how to do this but at least for
旅馆的冰河时代，例如石油高峰，如何做到这一点，但至少对于
people before he made it to the access and most of these people were opened for
人们在他进入之前，这些人中的大多数已经开放给
doing a chat or asking hackers after leaving in an individualist i can't
离开个人主义者后进行聊天或询问黑客，我不能
read this role i was a relief for be more showtime with this it necessary to
阅读这个角色，我很放心，因为有更多的表演时间，这是必要的
make an appointment but I know why in the netherlands
预约，但我知道为什么在荷兰
compair schedules cette date and time the hangout to the
compair安排cette的视频会议日期和时间
exact moment know that we should go to death cycle
确切的时刻知道我们应该进入死亡循环
again and again to ever social do not do with what or the chance it is people
一次又一次地与社会交往与人无关或与人无关
furious sweet mierlo because he starts to know more people and
愤怒的甜蜜mierlo，因为他开始认识更多的人，
show them a willingness to socialize the flap case opens and somehow it was
向他们表明愿意对翻盖案进行社交化的意愿
expected or mee when he keeps him regularly at baseclear spent my free
当他定期将他保持在baseclear时的期望值
time in social settings level of social control man collecte fast and everyone
在社会环境中的时间社会控制的人收集的速度很快，每个人
knows what ever your us doing this dusky living sense of seventeen and reward
知道您曾经做什么过我们这个十七岁的昏昏欲睡的生活并获得奖赏
show it can be very soft ok things both in some instances riley
表明在某些情况下，莱利都可以很柔软，还可以
holy ghost writer at nat dear to fame or excitement or you dees in one
亲爱的成名者或兴奋者中的圣灵鬼作家
other place just so acutely spent some time in
另一个地方如此急切地花了一些时间
solitude and recharge my battery and that point
孤独并为我的电池充电
ar realize that my situation in the western individualists country is a
意识到我在西方个人主义国家的处境是
sorbet yes it takes an effort to socialize but
果汁冰糕是，需要付出努力才能社交，但
at least privacy in solitude arndt difficult to find on the other hand
另一方面，至少在孤独中很难找到隐私
i'm back in the quietness of my apartment in the country where people berlino der
我回到了我在人们berlino der所在国家的公寓的宁静中
neighbors and prioritize individual goals like carriers money and material
邻居并确定个人目标的优先级，例如承运人的金钱和材料
professions about each other and new jersey chance that started loneliness
关于彼此的职业和开始寂寞的新泽西机会
pipa pony yes third difference between halloween
琵琶小马是万圣节之间的第三次区别
ascento lonis en solitude can be absolutely enjoyable
孤独的Ascento lonis绝对令人愉快
with whom thailand's arm who require at least some young connection to function
与谁的泰国手臂需要至少一些年轻的联系才能发挥作用
properly in the langres well there plenty of possibilities to
正确地在语言中有很多可能性
acquire this you increase my connection view finding a group of friends
获得这一点，可以增加我的联系视图，找到一群朋友
john in the clapping community that we follow your t-shirt and like activity
约翰在鼓掌社区中，我们关注您的T恤和喜欢的活动
sports club living is the mill get int his death
体育俱乐部的生存是磨坊生死
in the group's the larger bykans de pryce wie bij
在小组中更大的bykans de pryce wie bij
bitrate companionship in exchange for time or times for money and to be en
比特币的陪伴，以换取时间或金钱
insert part of a group of respect to continue the transactions and many cases
插入一组尊重以继续进行交易，在许多情况下
new york bacon de to conform to do group narrative
纽约培根符合组织叙事
the absurd en fx shirt en values ​​which might not be entirely compatible with
荒谬的en fx衬衫en价值观可能与
iphone espèce genre conform t-shirt and
iphoneespeèce风格符合T恤和
audiological or religious doctrine how should I especially bottle him
听觉学或宗教学说我应该怎么特别给他装瓶
berkum ii gold philosophically your site so how to think chicken on her buttocks
从哲学上来说，您的网站的原理是如此，如何在她的臀部上思考鸡肉
in the deep and the light and then the question rvc
在深处，然后是问题rvc
for the sole purpose of belonging and that formido the how sacrifice moreover even
出于归属和福美多的唯一目的，甚至如何牺牲
then i want to santing experienced in a ga that's that layma of loneliness
那我想在一个孤独的俗世中体验
that there aren't individualistic with just activism
没有个人主义而只有行动主义
what in social isolation billions of private or human connexion personally
在社会孤立的情况下，数十亿个人或个人的联系
he does want to sacrifice myself and my values ​​to be loved your shirt a group
他确实想牺牲自己和我的价值观被一群人爱上你的衬衫
party don't want to be socially isolated tide so it must be one
政党不想成为社会孤立的浪潮，所以它一定是一个
agent w
代理人
is that internet and on its perhaps keep out of connection or find with
是互联网及其上可能无法连接或与
people online so 2 percent is count the internet
上网的人是互联网的2％
give us the opportunity to connect with people around the group based on
让我们有机会与基于
specific interest this means skip the weekend
特别的兴趣，这意味着跳过周末
superficie jelle tee of small interpreter and micro interactions exclusively about the
小型口译人员的jeffee tee和专门针对以下内容的微观互动
things you want to the flipside is online interaction
你想要的另一面是在线互动
is still here the high tea simulacrum of pixels and megabytes of course with i
仍然是像素和兆字节的下午茶模拟物，当然与
deeper friendships develop online what the soft a ghost hand 'in them with
在网上发展更深厚的友谊
designer for real life mix which brings his back to the old skool face-to-face
现实生活中的混搭设计师，让他回到了旧的传统服装上
in athens communication that is more pure and complete with its
在雅典的交流中，它更加纯净和完善
non-verbal communication and minimal involvement of technology
非语言交流和最少的技术投入
there is nothing like kings ambon india touching body language at the end of the
没有什么比国王安汶印度人更能触及末尾的肢体语言了。
day this is what most people want when truly one to connect with someone that
今天，这就是大多数人想要的，当真正的一个人与某个人联系时
is why my belief my ep product exclusive shows live online and social
这就是为什么我相信我的ep产品独家展示在线和社交直播的原因
media in this course groups form sets edgar
本课程中的媒体分组形成edgar
silent and ow die private true you 'my connection is the difference between
沉默和欠个人隐私，真正的你是我的人与人之间的区别
watching 'for example de studio ferris from google street view and really be in
观看“例如Google街景中的摩天楼”，
their work no round feeling the station just
他们的工作没有圆满的感觉
briefing it if necessary a like the real thing however a good at exclude the
如果有必要，简报一下，就像真实的东西，但是擅长排除
possibility that some day weekend simplicity reality to such an extent
周末某天的简单现实达到如此程度的可能性
that how berlino tested infants so how to use of this guy glue of
那berlino如何测试婴儿，所以如何使用这家伙胶
loneliness a single it starts with the acceptance that social interaction ever
孤独感始于对社会交往的接受
requires some form of sacrifice eijsink for sanity it might be a good
需要某种形式的牺牲eijsink才能保持理智，这可能是一个好习惯
idea to make this sacrifice to certain degree with a color boundaries and
用颜色边界在某种程度上做出这种牺牲的想法，
with like-minded people that respect this by his death much joy in solitude
与志同道合的人通过他的死亡尊重这一点很孤独
whatever the muesli of loneliness and nurse also much joy in social connection
不管孤独和护士的牛奶什锦早餐在社交方面也很快乐
without losing it even in the week if you can find a healthy balance
如果您可以找到一个健康的平衡，即使在一周内也不会丢失它
the best of both worlds thank you for watching
两全其美谢谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]